{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When entering a tunnel during daytime, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn on the regular headlights (low beam) and slow down",
                "Sound the horn",
                "Turn on the regular headlights (low beam) and speed up"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn on the regular headlights (low beam) and slow down"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "At night, when driving behind another vehicle, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn on the normal headlights (low beam)",
                "Turn on the high beam",
                "Not use car headlights"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn on the normal headlights (low beam)"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If a car approaches from the other direction while your high beam is on, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn off lights",
                "Switch between high and low beam repetitively",
                "Switch to normal headlights (low beam) immediately"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Switch to normal headlights (low beam) immediately"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When filling up your car with gas, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Not care as it does not pose any threat",
                "Turn off the engine",
                "Keep the engine running"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn off the engine"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the traffic light turns yellow when your vehicle has already entered the intersection, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Stop immediately in the middle of the intersection",
                "Continue forward cautiously",
                "Stare at the traffic light"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Continue forward cautiously"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If you feel sleepy while driving, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Take amphetamines and continue driving",
                "Not be concerned as it will pass",
                "Stop immediately at the side of the road to get some rest"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Stop immediately at the side of the road to get some rest"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When approaching an intersection that has a traffic policeman regulating traffic and an active traffic light and fixed traffic sign, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Follow the traffic policeman s instructions",
                "Follow the traffic lights",
                "Heed the fixed traffic sign"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Follow the traffic policeman s instructions"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The moment you enter your vehicle, you should first perform the following necessary adjustments in order:",
            "answers": [
                "Adjust the seat, adjust the mirrors, and fasten the seat belt",
                "Fasten the seat belt, adjust the mirrors, and adjust your seat",
                "Fasten the seat belt, adjust the seat, and adjust the mirrors"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Adjust the seat, adjust the mirrors, and fasten the seat belt"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Everyday prior to driving the vehicle, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Listen to the weather forecast",
                "Do a routine check of the various vehicle systems",
                "Should not perform any routine checks as long as the engine is running"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Do a routine check of the various vehicle systems"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "It is okay while driving for the driver to:",
            "answers": [
                "Read the newspaper",
                "Use the phone",
                "Listen to the radio at a low volume"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Listen to the radio at a low volume"
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The driver and passengers should fasten their seat belt:",
            "answers": [
                "After a minute from setting off",
                "Prior to setting off",
                "Before turning on the car engine"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Before turning on the car engine"
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The purpose of the head rest is",
            "answers": [
                "To protect the neck in a rear end collision",
                "To be used as a pillow for sleeping during long trips",
                "To rest the head during the car trip"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "To protect the neck in a rear end collision"
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The drivers ability to focus is impaired during driving due to:",
            "answers": [
                "Having an abundance in energy",
                "Being sleepy and tired",
                "Driving inside the city"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Being sleepy and tired"
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Using a cell phone while driving impacts the drivers ability to drive in a:",
            "answers": [
                "Positive way",
                "Negative way",
                "Both positive and negative way"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Negative way"
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The first advice for a driver that cosumed some alcohol is to:",
            "answers": [
                "Drive at low speeds",
                "Refrain from driving until the side effects of alcohol have disappeared",
                "Not to be bothered"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Refrain from driving until the side effects of alcohol have disappeared"
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Driving under the influence of sleeping medication is:",
            "answers": [
                "Dangerous",
                "Delightful",
                "Not dangerous"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Dangerous"
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If the gas pedal gets stuck while driving, the driver should immediately:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn off the engine without locking the steering wheel",
                "Pull the handbrake up",
                "Change to a lower gear"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn off the engine without locking the steering wheel"
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If the car hood accidentally releases while driving down the road, you should immediately:",
            "answers": [
                "Increase your speed a little",
                "Reduce your speed gradually and pull to the side of the road",
                "Press firmly on the brakes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduce your speed gradually and pull to the side of the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "To avoid being late during heavy rain, the driver should start his journey:",
            "answers": [
                "A bit earlier than usual",
                "A bit later than usual",
                "With good spirits"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "A bit earlier than usual"
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Before stepping into the vehicle, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Make sure he has enough time on his hands",
                "Look around and under the vehicle",
                "Fasten the seatbelt"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Look around and under the vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving in heavy traffic, the driver should glance at his mirrors every:",
            "answers": [
                "45 seconds",
                "30 seconds",
                "4 to 8 seconds"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4 to 8 seconds"
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Before turning right, the driver should glance at:",
            "answers": [
                "The left side mirror only",
                "The right side mirror only",
                "All the mirrors, especially the right side mirror and blind spots"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All the mirrors, especially the right side mirror and blind spots"
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The biggest threat that vehicles parked on the right side pavement pose to drivers passing close to them is:",
            "answers": [
                "Pedestrians, and children, appearing suddenly from between these parked vehicles",
                "Trash being thrown from them towards the passing vehicles",
                "Loud sounds from the radios of these vehicles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Pedestrians, and children, appearing suddenly from between these parked vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The threat that vehicles parked on the right side pavement bring to drivers passing close to them is:",
            "answers": [
                "The fact that any of these parked vehicles could take off and join traffic at any time",
                "The alarm that would go off as the drivers cross next to these vehicles",
                "The oppening of a car trunk"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The fact that any of these parked vehicles could take off and join traffic at any time"
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "As a cautious driver, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Never yield your right of way",
                "Take the right of way by force as it is your right",
                "Yield the right of way to prevent road collisions"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Yield the right of way to prevent road collisions"
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving and prior to hitting your brakes, you should first look:",
            "answers": [
                "In the mirrors, namely the rear view mirror",
                "To your right",
                "To your left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In the mirrors, namely the rear view mirror"
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When strong braking is applied, ABS in modern vehicles:",
            "answers": [
                "Would normally cause the brake pedal to pulsate",
                "Would normally make noise and cause the brake pedal to pulsate",
                "Should not make noise or cause the brake pedal to pulsate"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Would normally make noise and cause the brake pedal to pulsate"
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "One of the benefits of ABS in modern vehicles when strong braking is applied, is:",
            "answers": [
                "Preventing brakes locking up only",
                "Not preventing brakes locking up and not helping the driver maintain steering control of the vehicle",
                "Preventing brakes from locking up and allows the driver to maintain steering control of the vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Preventing brakes locking up only"
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If your vehicle is beginning to",
            "answers": [
                "Press on the brakes and steer your vehicle",
                "in the opposite direction to your vehicles rear",
                "Get your foot off the accelerator (dont press on the brakes) and steer your vehicle in the same direction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Get your foot off the accelerator (dont press on the brakes) and steer your vehicle in the same direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If you leave a safe distance between your vehicle and the vehicle in front, you will be able to:",
            "answers": [
                "Avoid a collision with that vehicle should it make a sudden stoop",
                "Enjoy the view surrounding you",
                "Read the plate number of that vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Avoid a collision with that vehicle should it make a sudden stoop"
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the vehicle in front immediately takes off the moment a red light turns green, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Take off immediately after it and fast",
                "Sound your horn",
                "Make sure the road is empty then take off"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Make sure the road is empty then take off"
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When approaching an intersection with a flashing yellow traffic light, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Fasten the seatbelt",
                "Provide right of way",
                "Stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Provide right of way"
        },
        {
            "id": 33,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The seat belt must be used:",
            "answers": [
                "Not absolutely necessary",
                "By front seat passengers only",
                "By all passengers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "By all passengers"
        },
        {
            "id": 34,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If your vehicle suddenly malfunctions while driving on a highway, you should",
            "answers": [
                "Leave the highway from the nearest exit",
                "Stop the car immediately in the place your at",
                "Keep on driving to your destination"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Leave the highway from the nearest exit"
        },
        {
            "id": 35,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The driver should hold the steering wheel:",
            "answers": [
                "With one hand",
                "With both hands",
                "With his fingertips"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "With both hands"
        },
        {
            "id": 36,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Passengers of a loaded truck should not exceed:",
            "answers": [
                "One passenger",
                "The authorized number of passengers",
                "Are not entitled to transport passengers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The authorized number of passengers"
        },
        {
            "id": 37,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Upon coupling the trailer with the tractor, the driver should make sure that the:",
            "answers": [
                "Trailer brake is applied and its legs are lowered to the ground",
                "Trailer brake is released and its legs lowered are lowered to the ground",
                "One leg is lowered to the ground"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Trailer brake is applied and its legs are lowered to the ground"
        },
        {
            "id": 38,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "After coupling the trailer with the tractor, the driver should make sure that the:",
            "answers": [
                "Air pipes and electric lines are connected properly",
                "Air pipes only are connected properly",
                "Electric lines only are connected properly"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Air pipes and electric lines are connected properly"
        },
        {
            "id": 39,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When coupling the trailer to the",
            "answers": [
                "Reverse slowly above the trailer",
                "None",
                "Reverse quickly below the trailer"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reverse slowly above the trailer"
        },
        {
            "id": 40,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When uncoupling the trailer from the tractor, the driver must select a place:",
            "answers": [
                "With an incline and soft ground",
                "With a plane area and soft ground",
                "With an incline and solid ground"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "With a plane area and soft ground"
        },
        {
            "id": 41,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Upon uncoupling the trailer from the tractor, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Apply the trailer brake firmly and not lower its legs to the maximum",
                "Apply the trailer brake and lower its legs to the maximum",
                "Release the trailer brake and lower its legs to the maximum"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Apply the trailer brake and lower its legs to the maximum"
        },
        {
            "id": 42,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The heavy vehicle driver has numerous blind spots around his vehicle. The count of these blindspots is :",
            "answers": [
                "At least four",
                "At least eight",
                "Three"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "At least four"
        },
        {
            "id": 43,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The heavy vehicle driver should pay attention to the height of his vehicle especially:",
            "answers": [
                "When driving over a bridge",
                "When driving under a bridge or into a tunnel",
                "When driving on freeways"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "When driving under a bridge or into a tunnel"
        },
        {
            "id": 44,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The heavy vehicle driver should give special care for the width of his vehicle especially:",
            "answers": [
                "When driving on the freeway",
                "When taking a rest",
                "When overtaking another vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "When overtaking another vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 45,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The heavy vehicle driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Reverse in crowded places",
                "Reverse immediately after an intersection",
                "Avoid reversing in crowded places"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Avoid reversing in crowded places"
        },
        {
            "id": 46,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Dealing with heavy vehicles differs from smaller vehicles, thus when turning to the right, the driver of a heavy vehicle should:",
            "answers": [
                "Not allow enough distance to his right side",
                "Allow enough distance in the front",
                "Allow enough distance to his right side"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Allow enough distance to his right side"
        },
        {
            "id": 47,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In order to avoid your heavy vehicles rear left wheels from crossing the center line as you negotiate a left hand turn, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Take the extreme left at the turn",
                "Take the right a bit at the turn",
                "Increase your speed at the turn"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Take the right a bit at the turn"
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In order to avoid your heavy vehicles rear right wheels from skidding off the road as you negotiate a right hand turn, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Drive in the middle of the lane",
                "Take to the right at the turn",
                "Increase your speed at the turn"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Drive in the middle of the lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 49,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "As you approach a hill top, you should always expect behind the peak",
            "answers": [
                "A straight stretch of road",
                "Obstacles",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Obstacles"
        },
        {
            "id": 50,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving your heavy vehicle downhill and in order to keep control of your vehicle, you should mainly depend on using:",
            "answers": [
                "The brakes",
                "The hand brake",
                "An appropriate low gear"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "An appropriate low gear"
        },
        {
            "id": 51,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Using the main brakes of your heavy vehicle continuously when driving downhill for long disables the brakes due of:",
            "answers": [
                "Heat build up",
                "Break oil pressure",
                "Slope steepness"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Heat build up"
        },
        {
            "id": 52,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If the driver doesnt change quickly to a low gear as he starts to drive downhill, and the heavy vehicle gains speed:",
            "answers": [
                "It will be easy to change to a lower gear",
                "It will be impossible to change to a lower gear to have more control over the vehicle",
                "The driver will be able to overtake other vehicles safely"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "It will be impossible to change to a lower gear to have more control over the vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 53,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "As you drive your heavy vehicle uphill for a long period of time, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Avoid engine pressure build up",
                "Stick to driving on the left",
                "Prevent smaller vehicles from overtaking you"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Avoid engine pressure build up"
        },
        {
            "id": 54,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "As you drive your heavy vehicle uphill for a long period of time, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Check the fuel gauge continuously",
                "Keep to the extreme right as much as possible",
                "Keep to the extreme left as much as possible"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Keep to the extreme right as much as possible"
        },
        {
            "id": 55,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If you are going to overtake a vehcile uphill with your heavy vehicle and it will take too long, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Insist on overtaking",
                "Go beyond the speed limit",
                "Forget about overtaking the vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Forget about overtaking the vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 56,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When you are about to drive your heavy vehicle off road, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "You should keep an eye on the driver behind you",
                "Increase your speed a little",
                "Plan your path carefully"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Plan your path carefully"
        },
        {
            "id": 57,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Eye contact at the intersection:",
            "answers": [
                "Is a forum for drivers get to know one another",
                "Helps drivers avoid misunderstandings",
                "Is a sort of alert"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Helps drivers avoid misunderstandings"
        },
        {
            "id": 58,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "As a safety driving rule and whenever possible, the driver should avoid:",
            "answers": [
                "Reversing",
                "Slowing down gradually",
                "Washing his vehicle frequently"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reversing"
        },
        {
            "id": 59,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "By law, the driver should yield the right of way to:",
            "answers": [
                "Bus Schools flashing their hazard lights",
                "For women drivers",
                "Speeding vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Bus Schools flashing their hazard lights"
        },
        {
            "id": 60,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "By law, the driver should yield the right of way to:",
            "answers": [
                "Vehicles that are already in the roundabout",
                "Vehicles that are entering a roundabout",
                "Vehicles located to the right of the vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Vehicles that are already in the roundabout"
        },
        {
            "id": 61,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is legal to parallel park a vehicle to the pavement on a single lane two way street:",
            "answers": [
                "To the right of the direction of driving for the vehicle",
                "Doesnt matter as long as it doesnt hinder traffic",
                "To the left of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "To the right of the direction of driving for the vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 62,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Excessive eating:",
            "answers": [
                "Helps the driver drive more safely",
                "Will impair the drivers ability to react properly and make the right decisions",
                "Will allow the driver to maintain control of his vehicle while driving at very high speeds"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Will impair the drivers ability to react properly and make the right decisions"
        },
        {
            "id": 63,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Insufficient sleeping:",
            "answers": [
                "Helps improve reaction",
                "Slows down his reactions during driving and causes him a slight loss of memory",
                "Helps him to be alert"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slows down his reactions during driving and causes him a slight loss of memory"
        },
        {
            "id": 64,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In long trips, the driver must stop for rest every:",
            "answers": [
                "4 hours",
                "10 hours",
                "8 hours"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "4 hours"
        },
        {
            "id": 65,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In long trips, the driver must stop for rest around every:",
            "answers": [
                "900 kilometers",
                "750 kilometers",
                "250 kilometers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "250 kilometers"
        },
        {
            "id": 66,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Driving under the influence of alcohol:",
            "answers": [
                "Endangers driver s life as well as the lives of others",
                "Endangers others lives only",
                "Endangers the driver"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Endangers driver s life as well as the lives of others"
        },
        {
            "id": 67,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "During very long trips, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Consume amphetamines regularly",
                "Continue driving without rest",
                "Never consume amphetamines to stay awake"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Never consume amphetamines to stay awake"
        },
        {
            "id": 68,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The best way for a driver to know how a medical drug affects his driving is to:",
            "answers": [
                "Check with another driver",
                "Check with his physician",
                "Test it on another driver"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check with his physician"
        },
        {
            "id": 69,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Driving under the influence of alcohol or drugs causes the driver a false feeling of:",
            "answers": [
                "Fear",
                "Courage and boldness",
                "Outrage"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Courage and boldness"
        },
        {
            "id": 70,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When you are about to overtake",
            "answers": [
                "Rely on that vehicle light signals",
                "None",
                "Never depend on that vehicle s driver hand gestures"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Never depend on that vehicle s driver hand gestures"
        },
        {
            "id": 71,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Every heavy vehicle driver should be careful about his vehicle width especially when he:",
            "answers": [
                "Enters narrow places",
                "Stops for some rest",
                "Loads his cargo"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Enters narrow places"
        },
        {
            "id": 72,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When reversing, the driver of a heavy vehicle should depend on information:",
            "answers": [
                "From driving assistant",
                "From a rear view camera",
                "From mirrors"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "From driving assistant"
        },
        {
            "id": 73,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "After filling up a tanker, the driver should check that:",
            "answers": [
                "All release valves are securely fastened",
                "All the lids and release valves are securely fastened",
                "Some of the lids are securely fastened"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All the lids and release valves are securely fastened"
        },
        {
            "id": 74,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The motorcyclist can protect himself by:",
            "answers": [
                "Wearing motorcycle protective gear",
                "Driving the motorcycle on one wheel",
                "Ensure that there is insurance on the motorcycle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Wearing motorcycle protective gear"
        },
        {
            "id": 75,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The motorcycle protective leather suit can resist:",
            "answers": [
                "Friction with asphalt and small stones",
                "Fire",
                "Driving fast and straddling lanes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Friction with asphalt and small stones"
        },
        {
            "id": 76,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Motorcycle gloves protect:",
            "answers": [
                "The hands from cold and injuries",
                "The body from cold",
                "Better control of steering in slopes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The hands from cold and injuries"
        },
        {
            "id": 77,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Motorcycle boots protect:",
            "answers": [
                "The knees and thighs from cold",
                "The feet from dust",
                "The feet from injury, water, and cold"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The feet from injury, water, and cold"
        },
        {
            "id": 78,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The spine protective suit protect:",
            "answers": [
                "The chest and abdomen from heat and cold",
                "The spine and spinal cord from the rain",
                "The spine and spinal cord from injury"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The spine and spinal cord from injury"
        },
        {
            "id": 79,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The protective eye glasses protect:",
            "answers": [
                "Ears from cold",
                "Eyes from rain, wind sand, and insects",
                "Eyes from crying"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Eyes from rain, wind sand, and insects"
        },
        {
            "id": 80,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The motorcyclist helmet protects:",
            "answers": [
                "The spine",
                "The hearing sense from traffic noise",
                "From fatal head injuries"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "From fatal head injuries"
        },
        {
            "id": 81,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the motorcyclist wears the helmet improperly or fails to wear it while driving, this behavior:",
            "answers": [
                "Is normal",
                "Is illegal",
                "Is legal"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Is illegal"
        },
        {
            "id": 82,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the motorcyclist just carries the helmet but does not wear it while driving, the behavior:",
            "answers": [
                "Give the motorcyclist legal protection",
                "Does not give the motorcyclist legal protection",
                "Is wise"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Does not give the motorcyclist legal protection"
        },
        {
            "id": 83,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving at night, the motorcyclist should wear:",
            "answers": [
                "Dark colors",
                "A fluorescent suit",
                "A sports outfit"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "A fluorescent suit"
        },
        {
            "id": 84,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "To be seen while driving at night, the motorcyclist is advised to:",
            "answers": [
                "Attach luminous stripes",
                "Turn off his lights and attach luminous stripes",
                "Make squeaking noise with his brakes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Attach luminous stripes"
        },
        {
            "id": 85,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If the motorcycle is equipped with a hydraulic brake system, then the driver should periodically:",
            "answers": [
                "Check the level of brake fluid",
                "Limit the use of brakes",
                "Check the level of brake line"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check the level of brake fluid"
        },
        {
            "id": 86,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The tread depth of the motorcycle tires should not be less than:",
            "answers": [
                "5 millimeters",
                "3 millimeters",
                "6 millimeters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "3 millimeters"
        },
        {
            "id": 87,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In order to steer the motorcycle freely, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Sit away from the steering grips",
                "Sit close to the steering grips",
                "Hold the steering grips with one hand"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Sit close to the steering grips"
        },
        {
            "id": 88,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In order to avoid unintended speed increase, the motorcyclist should hold the steering grip in such a way that his:",
            "answers": [
                "Right wrist is downwards",
                "Right wrist is upwards",
                "Left wrist is upwards"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Right wrist is downwards"
        },
        {
            "id": 89,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "For motorcycles, the braking process is most effective when the motorcyclist uses:",
            "answers": [
                "His feet, by pressing them on the asphalt",
                "Back brakes only",
                "Both back and front brakes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Both back and front brakes"
        },
        {
            "id": 90,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "For motorcycles to avoid skidding while severe braking, the motorcycle should be:",
            "answers": [
                "In a curve",
                "In a straight direction",
                "At an intersection"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In a straight direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 91,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Two causes for a motorcycle to squid on the road:",
            "answers": [
                "Low speed and low gear",
                "Slippery road and nervous reaction",
                "Broken lights and weak battery"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slippery road and nervous reaction"
        },
        {
            "id": 92,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving your motorcycle at night, you should drive:",
            "answers": [
                "Slowly and maintain a longer stopping distance",
                "Fast, with your low beam on",
                "Slowly and maintain a shorter stopping distance"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slowly and maintain a longer stopping distance"
        },
        {
            "id": 93,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When the motorcycle vibrates in",
            "answers": [
                "Uneven rotation of a least one wheel or",
                "one tire",
                "Even rotation of both wheels and both tires"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Uneven rotation of a least one wheel or"
        },
        {
            "id": 94,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "One of the main causes for motorcycle crash is the presence of:",
            "answers": [
                "Oil and pebbles on the road surface",
                "Inappropriate speed",
                "Policemen and traffic lights"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Inappropriate speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 95,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "To avoid motorcycle accidents at intersections you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Slow down and move to the appropriate lane",
                "Depend on your mirrors",
                "Overtake from the right of the vehicles stoped at the intersection"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slow down and move to the appropriate lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 96,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A motorcyclist is legally allowed to pass vehicles:",
            "answers": [
                "From any side",
                "From their right side",
                "From their left side"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "From their left side"
        },
        {
            "id": 97,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When you overtake with your motorcycle a vehicle from the left side, you should always remember that this vehicle may:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn on its hazard lights",
                "Decrease its speed gradually",
                "Swerve left suddenly"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Swerve left suddenly"
        },
        {
            "id": 98,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "While driving your motorcycle in a straight direction, you should always remember that an oncoming vehicle may:",
            "answers": [
                "Swerve suddenly into your path",
                "Stop suddenly on its path",
                "Swerve suddenly away from your path"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Swerve suddenly into your path"
        },
        {
            "id": 99,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If you have the habit of passing vehicles with your motorcycle in a zigzag manner, this means:",
            "answers": [
                "Your chances of being involved in an accident are much higher",
                "Your chances of being involved in an accident are much lower",
                "You are a world champion"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Your chances of being involved in an accident are much higher"
        },
        {
            "id": 100,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you drive your motorcycle with an intentionally emptied exhaust system producing a very loud noisy sound, it:",
            "answers": [
                "Makes people respect your creative ideas",
                "Is considered a clear traffic violation",
                "Is legal"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Is considered a clear traffic violation"
        },
        {
            "id": 101,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What are the environmental benefits of eco friendly driving? (select all that apply)",
            "answers": [
                "Reduction in local air pollutant levels",
                "Increase of greenhouse gas emissions (CO2)",
                "Reduction in road traffic"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduction in local air pollutant levels"
        },
        {
            "id": 102,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Whatare the savings benefits of eco driving? (select all that apply)",
            "answers": [
                "Lower insurance cost",
                "Lower vehicle maintenance costs",
                "Savings up to 50  in fuel and money"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Lower vehicle maintenance costs"
        },
        {
            "id": 103,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "How does eco friendly driving maintain the safety of the driver?",
            "answers": [
                "Improves road safety",
                "Improves driving skills",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 104,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What are the social responsibility benefits of eco driving?",
            "answers": [
                "Avoids stress while driving",
                "Increases comfort for drivers and passengers",
                "Sudden braking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Avoids stress while driving"
        },
        {
            "id": 106,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is the optimal speed range for eco friendly driving?",
            "answers": [
                "80 km/h   100 km/h",
                "50 km/h   80 km/h",
                "40 km/h   50 km/h"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "50 km/h   80 km/h"
        },
        {
            "id": 107,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is the maximum RPM level that should not be exceeded?",
            "answers": [
                "2000 RPM",
                "4000 RPM",
                "3000 RPM"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2000 RPM"
        },
        {
            "id": 108,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is the result of exceeding 2000 RPM?",
            "answers": [
                "It consumes less fuel",
                "It increases the temperature of the engine",
                "It consumes more fuel"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "It consumes more fuel"
        },
        {
            "id": 109,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is the result of fast starts and hard braking?",
            "answers": [
                "Wastes fuel",
                "Wears out tires and brakes more quickly",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 110,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "By how much is fuel consumption reduced when you change the oil and oil filterd regularly?",
            "answers": [
                "1  to 2 ",
                "1  to 3 ",
                "2  to 3 "
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "1  to 2 "
        },
        {
            "id": 111,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Which type of oil is best for the environment?",
            "answers": [
                "Energy conserving oil which has additives that reduce friction",
                "Energy conserving oil which has additives that increase friction",
                "Energy conserving oil which has additives that eliminate friction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Energy conserving oil which has additives that reduce friction"
        },
        {
            "id": 112,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "How do you ensure long lasitng tyres?",
            "answers": [
                "Check tire pressure at least once a year to preserve a low rolling resistance",
                "Change the tires each year",
                "Check tire pressure at least once a month to preserve a low rolling resistance"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check tire pressure at least once a month to preserve a low rolling resistance"
        },
        {
            "id": 113,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is the benefit of cleaning your air filters regularly?",
            "answers": [
                "All of the above",
                "Improved engine performance by 6 to 11 ",
                "Reduce air pollution"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 114,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What shoud you do when your car stops moving for more than a minute?",
            "answers": [
                "Turn it off",
                "Put it on neutral",
                "Do nothing"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn it off"
        },
        {
            "id": 115,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "How do you enhance the performance of your engine and reduce emission levels?",
            "answers": [
                "Change the engine s water regularly",
                "Use clean fuel that complies with international standards",
                "Buy a new engine"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Use clean fuel that complies with international standards"
        },
        {
            "id": 116,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What should you always check after filling your fuel tank?",
            "answers": [
                "Fuel tank cap is securely closed",
                "Fuel tank cap is open",
                "Car temperature is stable"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Fuel tank cap is securely closed"
        },
        {
            "id": 117,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Why is it preferable to park in the shade?",
            "answers": [
                "Reduces the pressure on the air conditioner",
                "Decreases fuel consumption",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 118,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "By how much does the frequent use of air conditioning increase fuel consumption?",
            "answers": [
                "0.1",
                "0.3",
                "0.2"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "0.1"
        },
        {
            "id": 119,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Which of the following reduces fuel consumption? (select all that applies)",
            "answers": [
                "Driving during peak times",
                "Traveling Light",
                "Driving at random speed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Traveling Light"
        },
        {
            "id": 120,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "What is eco friendly driving?",
            "answers": [
                "Eco Friendly Driving is the efficient use of lighting in driving through a simple method and smart water consumption",
                "Eco Friendly Driving is the efficient use of fuel in road transportation through easy, smart, and socially responsible driving practices that help cut fuel consumption and reduce air pollution from land transportation.",
                "Eco Friendly Driving is the efficient use of fuel in road transportation through easy, smart, and socially responsible driving practices that help increase fuel consumption and air pollution from land transportation."
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Eco Friendly Driving is the efficient use of fuel in road transportation through easy, smart, and socially responsible driving practices that help cut fuel consumption and reduce air pollution from land transportation."
        },
        {
            "id": 121,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, uneven road ahead",
                "Caution, slippery road ahead",
                "Caution, speed bumps ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, uneven road ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 122,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Roundabout ahead",
                "Caution, left bend ahead",
                "Caution, right bend ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, right bend ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 123,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, left bend ahead",
                "Caution, right bend ahead",
                "Vehicles can go left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, left bend ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 124,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, double lane road",
                "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the left",
                "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 125,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, double lane road",
                "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the left",
                "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, double bend ahead, first one to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 126,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, narrow road ahead",
                "Caution, dangerous slope",
                "Caution, slippery road ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, slippery road ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 127,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unsecure crossing",
                "No entry",
                "Caution, students or school"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, students or school"
        },
        {
            "id": 128,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, animals",
                "Stray animals",
                "Animals not allowed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, animals"
        },
        {
            "id": 129,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, double lane road",
                "Caution, intersetion without right of way",
                "Travel on the right side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, double lane road"
        },
        {
            "id": 130,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, various dangers",
                "You cannot turn",
                "Caution, roundabout ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, roundabout ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 131,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, intersection ahead",
                "Caution, intersection with no right of way",
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, intersection ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 132,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way",
                "Merging with a freeway",
                "Caution, intersection with no right of way"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way"
        },
        {
            "id": 133,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, intersection on the right",
                "Caution, intersection with no right of way",
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, intersection with no right of way"
        },
        {
            "id": 134,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Road with priority right of way",
                "End of speed limit",
                "One minute parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Road with priority right of way"
        },
        {
            "id": 135,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry for pedestrians",
                "Caution, pedestrian crossing",
                "Not reserved for pedestrians"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, pedestrian crossing"
        },
        {
            "id": 136,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Trolley crossing",
                "No entry for bikes",
                "Caution, cycles crossing"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, cycles crossing"
        },
        {
            "id": 137,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, wide road",
                "Caution, narrow road on the left",
                "Caution, narrow road ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, narrow road ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 138,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Priority to the right",
                "Narrow road on the right",
                "Caution, narrow road on the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, narrow road on the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 139,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way",
                "End of priority",
                "Caution, narrow road on the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, narrow road on the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 140,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, narrow road ahead",
                "Caution, falling or fallen rocks ahead",
                "Mountainous area"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, falling or fallen rocks ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 141,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to all types of motor vehicles",
                "Caution, electrical signs",
                "Caution, roundabout ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, electrical signs"
        },
        {
            "id": 142,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry",
                "Give way   priority road ahead",
                "Caution, various dangers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, various dangers"
        },
        {
            "id": 143,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry",
                "Give way   priority road ahead",
                "Caution, various dangers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Give way   priority road ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 144,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry",
                "End of priority",
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of priority"
        },
        {
            "id": 145,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No overtaking for all kinds of vehicles",
                "End of priority",
                "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, vehicles coming from the opposite direction have the right of way"
        },
        {
            "id": 146,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "One lane road",
                "No entry",
                "Stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Stop"
        },
        {
            "id": 147,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry for all motor vehicles",
                "One Lane road",
                "No parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry for all motor vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 148,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry",
                "Various dangers",
                "No parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry"
        },
        {
            "id": 149,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No overtaking allowed for trucks",
                "No overtaking allowed for all kinds of vehicles",
                "No entry"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No overtaking allowed for all kinds of vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 150,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lower Speed limit: 80 km/hour",
                "Give way   priority road ahead",
                "Upper speed limit: 30 km/hour"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Upper speed limit: 30 km/hour"
        },
        {
            "id": 151,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Theatre",
                "No parking",
                "You are not allowed to sound your horn"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You are not allowed to sound your horn"
        },
        {
            "id": 152,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Road reserved for trucks",
                "Trucks can overtake",
                "Trucks cannot overtake"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Trucks cannot overtake"
        },
        {
            "id": 153,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Animal carts allowed",
                "No entry for pedestrians",
                "No entry for animal carts"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry for animal carts"
        },
        {
            "id": 154,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to all types of motor vehicles",
                "Caution, Lane reserved for pedestrians",
                "No entry for pedestrians"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry for pedestrians"
        },
        {
            "id": 155,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry for bikes",
                "Compulsory path for motor vehicles",
                "Lane reserved for bikes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry for bikes"
        },
        {
            "id": 156,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry for motorbikes",
                "Cycles crossing",
                "Motorbikes Lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry for motorbikes"
        },
        {
            "id": 157,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Trolleys cannot be parked here",
                "Lane reserved for trolleys",
                "Not entry for trolleys"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Not entry for trolleys"
        },
        {
            "id": 158,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No parking",
                "Road reserved for motor vehicles",
                "No entry to all types of motor vehicles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to all types of motor vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 159,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 2.3m in height",
                "No entry for trucks",
                "No entry to cars exceeding 2.3m in width"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to cars exceeding 2.3m in width"
        },
        {
            "id": 160,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Compulsory direction for trucks",
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 3.5 tons in weight",
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 3.5 m in height"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to trucks exceeding 3.5 m in height"
        },
        {
            "id": 161,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Cargo cannot exceed 10m",
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 10m in height",
                "No entry to trucks carrying more than 6.5 tons of cargo"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to trucks exceeding 10m in height"
        },
        {
            "id": 162,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 7m in height",
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 7 tons/wheel",
                "No entry to trucks carrying more than 7 tons of cargo"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to trucks carrying more than 7 tons of cargo"
        },
        {
            "id": 163,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "End of restriction sign",
                "Start of restriction signs",
                "No speeding"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of restriction sign"
        },
        {
            "id": 164,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "End of speed limit",
                "Speed limit",
                "Start of speed limit"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of speed limit"
        },
        {
            "id": 165,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Compulsory direction to the left",
                "You cannot turn right",
                "Turn right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn right"
        },
        {
            "id": 166,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot turn left",
                "Turn left",
                "You can go straight or turn right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turn left"
        },
        {
            "id": 167,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot go right or left",
                "You must go straight",
                "You can turn right or left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You can turn right or left"
        },
        {
            "id": 168,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Trucks must go right",
                "You cannot turn left",
                "You can go straight or turn right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You can go straight or turn right"
        },
        {
            "id": 169,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot go left",
                "Compulsory direction to the left",
                "You can go straight or turn left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You can go straight or turn left"
        },
        {
            "id": 170,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You can go right",
                "Freeway lane",
                "Compulsory direction to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Compulsory direction to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 171,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot turn right",
                "You must go straight",
                "Compulsory direction to the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Compulsory direction to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 172,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Vehicle can only turn right",
                "Compulsory direction to the right or the left",
                "You cannot turn right or left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Vehicle can only turn right"
        },
        {
            "id": 173,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lane reserved for pedestrians and bicycles",
                "Lane reserved for bicycles",
                "End of bicycle track"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of bicycle track"
        },
        {
            "id": 174,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lane reserved for pedestrians and bicycles",
                "End of bicycle track",
                "No entry for pedestrians and bicycles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Lane reserved for pedestrians and bicycles"
        },
        {
            "id": 175,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Traffic direction",
                "You cannot turn right",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You cannot turn right"
        },
        {
            "id": 176,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Compulsory turn",
                "Traffic direction",
                "You cannot turn"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You cannot turn"
        },
        {
            "id": 177,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "End of no bus overtaking zone",
                "Lane reserved for buses",
                "No entry to buses"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to buses"
        },
        {
            "id": 178,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to trucks exceeding 6.5 tons in weight",
                "Lane reserved for trucks",
                "No entry to trucks"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to trucks"
        },
        {
            "id": 179,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No entry to trucks carrying more than 6.5 tons of cargo",
                "Compulsory direction for trucks",
                "Trucks cannot park here"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No entry to trucks carrying more than 6.5 tons of cargo"
        },
        {
            "id": 180,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Not entry to trailer trucks",
                "Compulsory direction for trucks",
                "No entry for trucks carrying Hazardous Material"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Not entry to trailer trucks"
        },
        {
            "id": 181,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "One minute parking for agricultural machinery",
                "Road reserved for agricultural machinery",
                "Agricultural machinery not allowed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Agricultural machinery not allowed"
        },
        {
            "id": 182,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, two lane road",
                "End of no overtaking zone",
                "End of no overtaking for trucks"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of no overtaking zone"
        },
        {
            "id": 183,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "End of no overtaking for trucks",
                "Caution, two lane road",
                "Trucks only"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of no overtaking for trucks"
        },
        {
            "id": 184,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No parking",
                "No overtaking for all kinds of vehicles",
                "No entry"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No parking"
        },
        {
            "id": 185,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No stopping and no parking",
                "No parking",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No stopping and no parking"
        },
        {
            "id": 186,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No parking in this zone",
                "No entry in this direction",
                "You must go straight"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You must go straight"
        },
        {
            "id": 187,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Direction to the left",
                "No parking on the left",
                "You cannot turn left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Direction to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 188,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Direction to the right",
                "No parking on the right",
                "You cannot turn right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Direction to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 189,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Parking zone",
                "Roundabout ahead",
                "You cannot turn"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Roundabout ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 190,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot park for more than 30 minutes",
                "Mandatory upper speed",
                "Mandatory lower speed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Mandatory lower speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 191,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Maximum speed: 30 km/h",
                "You cannot park for more than 30 minutes",
                "End of mandatory lower speed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of mandatory lower speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 192,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, slippery road ahead",
                "Tyre chains must be removed",
                "Vehicles equipped with metal chains only"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Vehicles equipped with metal chains only"
        },
        {
            "id": 193,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Park",
                "No entry for pedestrians",
                "Lane reserved for pedestrians"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Lane reserved for pedestrians"
        },
        {
            "id": 194,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lane reserved for pedestrians",
                "Upper ground pedestrian crossing",
                "End of pedestrian Lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of pedestrian Lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 195,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bicycles track",
                "No parking for bicycles",
                "No entry for bicycles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Bicycles track"
        },
        {
            "id": 196,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Cannot turn left",
                "Compulsory direction to the left",
                "No parking on the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Cannot turn left"
        },
        {
            "id": 197,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, moving bridge ahead",
                "Two  lane road connected to a bridge",
                "Hospital"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Hospital"
        },
        {
            "id": 198,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, pedestrian crossing",
                "End of pedestrian lane",
                "Caution, no entry to pedestrians"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, pedestrian crossing"
        },
        {
            "id": 199,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lane reseved for bikes",
                "Bicycle track",
                "No entry for bicycles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Lane reseved for bikes"
        },
        {
            "id": 200,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lanes merge ahead",
                "Merger with a freeway ahead",
                "Dead end road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Dead end road"
        },
        {
            "id": 201,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, airport runway",
                "Caution, bridge",
                "Highway"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Highway"
        },
        {
            "id": 202,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bridge above the road",
                "End of freeway",
                "Caution, narrow road ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "End of freeway"
        },
        {
            "id": 203,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, rough road ahead",
                "Bridge",
                "Tunnel"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Tunnel"
        },
        {
            "id": 204,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Help center",
                "Parking for the disabled",
                "For doctors only"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Help center"
        },
        {
            "id": 205,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No parking for the disabled",
                "One minute parking",
                "Parking reserved for the disabled"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Parking reserved for the disabled"
        },
        {
            "id": 206,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Parking",
                "One minute parking",
                "Parking not allowed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "One minute parking"
        },
        {
            "id": 207,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Parking for all   not more than two taxi cars allowed",
                "Taxis not allowed to park here",
                "Taxi stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Taxi stop"
        },
        {
            "id": 208,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Remove immediately",
                "Inquiries",
                "Police"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Police"
        },
        {
            "id": 209,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Internet Center",
                "Petrol station",
                "Inquiries"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Inquiries"
        },
        {
            "id": 210,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Parking reserved for the police",
                "Fire Brigade",
                "Municipality police"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Municipality police"
        },
        {
            "id": 211,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Freeway",
                "Dangerous interesection ahead",
                "Indirect turn to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Freeway"
        },
        {
            "id": 212,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "No parking",
                "Parking",
                "One minute parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Parking"
        },
        {
            "id": 213,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Repair Center",
                "Restaurant",
                "Hotel"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Hotel"
        },
        {
            "id": 214,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Inquiries",
                "Restaurant",
                "Refreshments"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Restaurant"
        },
        {
            "id": 215,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Public phone",
                "Restaurant",
                "Petrol station"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Public phone"
        },
        {
            "id": 216,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Petrol station",
                "Repair Center",
                "Restaurant"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Petrol station"
        },
        {
            "id": 217,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Lane reserved for buses",
                "Buses are not allowed to stop here",
                "Bus parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Bus parking"
        },
        {
            "id": 218,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Help Center",
                "Camping   camping cars zone",
                "No parking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Camping   camping cars zone"
        },
        {
            "id": 219,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bend ahead",
                "Reduce Speed",
                "Indirect bend to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Bend ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 220,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Bend ahead",
                "Reduce Speed",
                "Indirect bend to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Indirect bend to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 221,
            "category": "Signs",
            "question": "",
            "answers": [
                "Caution, right bend ahead",
                "Caution, road Bumps ahead",
                "Caution, uneven roads ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Caution, road Bumps ahead"
        },
        {
            "id": 222,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the road is divided into two lanes with solid lines or other lane seperator, the driver:",
            "answers": [
                "Should travel in the opposite direction",
                "Should cross these lines and drive on it",
                "Should not cross these lines or other lane seperators"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Should not cross these lines or other lane seperators"
        },
        {
            "id": 223,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In case of normal traffic, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Keep to the left side of the road",
                "Cross the dividing lines to overtake",
                "Keep to the right side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Keep to the right side of the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 224,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the Lane is marked with o solid line and o broken line, which one of the following statements is correct?",
            "answers": [
                "The driver may change lanes if the broken line is to the left",
                "The driver may not change lanes if the solid line is to the left",
                "The driver may change lanes if the solid line is to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver may change lanes if the solid line is to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 225,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Pavements are intended:",
            "answers": [
                "To park vehicles, when parking is allowed",
                "To be used by pedestrians, children trolleys, the sick , and the disabled",
                "To put anything that obstructs the use of the pavement"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "To be used by pedestrians, children trolleys, the sick , and the disabled"
        },
        {
            "id": 226,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When drastically changing speed or direction, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Cross the solid line if the solid line is on his left",
                "Cross the broken line without any signaling",
                "Check there is no danger, and give appropriate signals to other road users"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check there is no danger, and give appropriate signals to other road users"
        },
        {
            "id": 227,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Sudden braking is allowed only:",
            "answers": [
                "In case of danger",
                "If the driver needs to stop the car",
                "If the driver needs to test the brakes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In case of danger"
        },
        {
            "id": 228,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The driver should keep to:",
            "answers": [
                "The right, when another vehicle is heading towards him way from the opposite direction",
                "The left, when another driver is overtaking him",
                "The left, when another vehicle is heading towards him way from the opposite direction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The right, when another vehicle is heading towards him way from the opposite direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 229,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Overtake from the left when there is enough visibility",
                "Travel on the right side of the road when another vehicle is heading towards him from the opposite direction",
                "Overtake traveling military or police motorcades, or other processions"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Overtake traveling military or police motorcades, or other processions"
        },
        {
            "id": 230,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Travel in the designated direction",
                "Drive in neutral with the intention to drive the vehicle solely through downforce",
                "Move slowly on the left side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Drive in neutral with the intention to drive the vehicle solely through downforce"
        },
        {
            "id": 231,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Travel in the designated direction",
                "Make a U turn in the middle of the road in a populated area"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Make a U turn in the middle of the road in a populated area"
        },
        {
            "id": 232,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Travel in the designated direction",
                "Travel in other than the designated direction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Travel in other than the designated direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 233,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Travel on the right side of the road",
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Wash their vehicles on the freeway"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Wash their vehicles on the freeway"
        },
        {
            "id": 234,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The driver:",
            "answers": [
                "Should not take into consideration the condition of the road or the traffic density",
                "Should increase his speed when visibility is low",
                "Should reduce his speed or stop completely when the conditions surrounding him dictate so, especially when visibility is really bad"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Should reduce his speed or stop completely when the conditions surrounding him dictate so, especially when visibility is really bad"
        },
        {
            "id": 235,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Overtake from the left",
                "Take the left",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Overtake from the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 236,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When a driver is passing a vehicle, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Keep to the right side of the road as much as possible with other road users around",
                "Keep to the left side of the road as much as possible with other road users around",
                "Keep to the midlde if it is a single lane road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Keep to the right side of the road as much as possible with other road users around"
        },
        {
            "id": 237,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Before overtaking, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Should not take into consideration driving decorum when in populated areas",
                "Overtake, even if the driver behind have have already initiated a similar overtake",
                "Check that drivers behind him have not initiated a similar overtake"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check that drivers behind him have not initiated a similar overtake"
        },
        {
            "id": 238,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Before overtaking, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Know that he has the right to overtake even if the driver behind him is overtaking him",
                "Not alert the driver that he is about to overtake",
                "Alert the driver he is about to overtake"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Alert the driver he is about to overtake"
        },
        {
            "id": 239,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When overtaking, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Not keep to the right immediately before overtaking",
                "Use the left side of the road, even if it disaccommodate drivers traveling on the opposite direction",
                "Use the left side of the road without disaccommodating drivers traveling on the opposite direction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Use the left side of the road without disaccommodating drivers traveling on the opposite direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 240,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "As an exception to the rule, overtaking from the right is allowed:",
            "answers": [
                "If the driver signals that he is moving to the right",
                "Overtaking from the right is not allowed",
                "On roads that accomomdate more than two lanes, provided that the drivers movement between lanes does accommodate or does not put other road users at risk"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "On roads that accomomdate more than two lanes, provided that the drivers movement between lanes does accommodate or does not put other road users at risk"
        },
        {
            "id": 241,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is prohibited to overtake:",
            "answers": [
                "A vehicle from the left, if the road is marked with broken lines",
                "If the road is broken into multiple lanes with broken lines",
                "On bends"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "On bends"
        },
        {
            "id": 242,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is prohibited to overtake:",
            "answers": [
                "On single lane roads",
                "From the right, whatever the case may be",
                "On bridges and in tunnels"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "On bridges and in tunnels"
        },
        {
            "id": 243,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is prohibited to overtake:",
            "answers": [
                "In case vehicles have stopped because of a traffic obstruction or a sign to do so",
                "If the left side of the road will be clear after the overtake",
                "If the vehicle you are overtaking is traveling on the right side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In case vehicles have stopped because of a traffic obstruction or a sign to do so"
        },
        {
            "id": 244,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is prohibited to overtake:",
            "answers": [
                "At the top edge of ascents, when there is not enough visibility ahead, and when the left side of the road will be clear after the takeover",
                "When the width of the road make for a very easy and safe overtake",
                "If the road is broken into multiple lanes with broken lines"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "At the top edge of ascents, when there is not enough visibility ahead, and when the left side of the road will be clear after the takeover"
        },
        {
            "id": 245,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If a police car, ambulance, or fire truck gives a signal of approaching, other road users should:",
            "answers": [
                "Stop immediately where they are so as to ease the movement of such vehicle",
                "Increase their speed so as to ease the movement of such vehicle",
                "Reduce their speed, and if need be, stop or move aside so as to ease the movemen of such vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduce their speed, and if need be, stop or move aside so as to ease the movemen of such vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 246,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is prohibited to overtake:",
            "answers": [
                "If the road is broken into multiple lanes with broken lines",
                "On narrow or steep mountain road",
                "On wide roads"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "On narrow or steep mountain road"
        },
        {
            "id": 247,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "On approaching an intersection, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Keep to the right side of the road",
                "Check that the road he is about to cross is clear",
                "Keep moving without checking first that the road is clear"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Check that the road he is about to cross is clear"
        },
        {
            "id": 248,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A driver who is about to leave the road he is on to another road on the right should:",
            "answers": [
                "Tilt a little to the left but remain on the road",
                "Keep to the left side of the road",
                "Keep to the right side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Keep to the right side of the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 249,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A driver who is about to leave the road he is on to another road on the left should:",
            "answers": [
                "Keep to the middle, without tilting left or right",
                "Tilt a little to the right but remain on the road",
                "Tilt a little to the left but remain on the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Tilt a little to the left but remain on the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 250,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the driver is about to leave on road and get on another one, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Titlt slowly to the right",
                "Make the appropriate turn with utmost speed so as not to misaccommodate others",
                "None"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Titlt slowly to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 251,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is best to keep a \"safe Distance\":",
            "answers": [
                "From all sides of the vehicle",
                "From the left and the right sides only",
                "From the front and the end sides only"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "From all sides of the vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 252,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is important to allow a \"safe distance\" because",
            "answers": [
                "It gives drivers the time to react to what happens",
                "It gives other vehicles a chance to enter the lane",
                "It prevents distraction with other vehicles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "It gives drivers the time to react to what happens"
        },
        {
            "id": 253,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A solid green light at the intersection means:",
            "answers": [
                "You should stop and check traffic in the other direction before you carry on",
                "You cannot turn right",
                "You can cross the intersetion if it is posisble"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You can cross the intersetion if it is posisble"
        },
        {
            "id": 254,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A flashing yellow light means:",
            "answers": [
                "You can carry on if the road is clear",
                "You should stop and carry on only when the road is clear",
                "Reduce your speed and carry on cautiously"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduce your speed and carry on cautiously"
        },
        {
            "id": 255,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A yellow light on the intersection means:",
            "answers": [
                "Go ahead",
                "Reduce your speed and be ready to stop",
                "Stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduce your speed and be ready to stop"
        },
        {
            "id": 256,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If you have a flat tyre while youre traveling:",
            "answers": [
                "Let the steering wheel take the reigns",
                "Release the accelerator to allow the vehicle to slow down, keep the steering wheel straight, and pull off the road",
                "Press on the brakes to slow down, and pull off the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Release the accelerator to allow the vehicle to slow down, keep the steering wheel straight, and pull off the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 257,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If the lights of the vehicle traveling on the opposite direction are bothering you, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Look towards the middle of the road",
                "Look towards the left side of the road",
                "Look down, and towards the right side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Look down, and towards the right side of the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 258,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In case of vehicle break down on the highway",
            "answers": [
                "Wait inside the vehicle until the road assistance vehicle reaches you",
                "Place the warning triangle and turn on the headlights to warn other drivers",
                "Place the warning triangle and activate all four signal lights to warn other drivers"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Wait inside the vehicle until the road assistance vehicle reaches you"
        },
        {
            "id": 259,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you enter a highway, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Slow down",
                "Drive below the speed limit",
                "The driver may not change lanes if the broken line is to the left"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver may not change lanes if the broken line is to the left"
        },
        {
            "id": 261,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If a vehicle is pressing behind you, and you are on the left lane on a freeway, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Speed up",
                "Press the brakes intermittently to drive the other vehicle to move away",
                "Move to the right lane, and adjust your speed to the traffic speed on that lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Move to the right lane, and adjust your speed to the traffic speed on that lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 262,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "If your brakes stops working while you are on the road, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Quickly press on the brakes with high frequency",
                "Head directly to a repair shop",
                "Turn off the engine"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Quickly press on the brakes with high frequency"
        },
        {
            "id": 263,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "In case of bad weather, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Drive below the upper speed limit so as to accommodate road conditions",
                "Drive at the upper speed limit and turn on the lights",
                "Drive at the upper speed limit"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Drive below the upper speed limit so as to accommodate road conditions"
        },
        {
            "id": 264,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The driver needs a bigger \"safe distance\":",
            "answers": [
                "Where there are other cars in front",
                "On dry roads",
                "On wet roads"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "On wet roads"
        },
        {
            "id": 265,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Pavements are intended:",
            "answers": [
                "To put away anything that obstructs the use of the road",
                "To park vehicles, when parking is allowed",
                "To be used by pedestrians, children trolleys, by the sick and the disabled"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "To be used by pedestrians, children trolleys, by the sick and the disabled"
        },
        {
            "id": 266,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Rear brake lights alert other drivers that you are:",
            "answers": [
                "Entering a bend",
                "Changing lanes",
                "Slowing down or stopping"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slowing down or stopping"
        },
        {
            "id": 267,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "On a four way intersection, the vehicle that goes first is:",
            "answers": [
                "The vehicle that arrived first and already entered the intersection",
                "The vehicle that arrived first",
                "The vehicle that is turning right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The vehicle that arrived first and already entered the intersection"
        },
        {
            "id": 268,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "You should stop when you see:",
            "answers": [
                "A flashing red light",
                "A solid yellow light",
                "A flashing yellow light"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "A flashing red light"
        },
        {
            "id": 269,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you are sharing the road",
            "answers": [
                "Require a smaller turning radius",
                "Require less time to overtake in descents",
                "Need a bigger safe distance with other vehicles to be able to stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Require a smaller turning radius"
        },
        {
            "id": 270,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "When turning right at the green light, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Slow down to be able to make the turn",
                "Carry on on the same lane",
                "Give way to pedestrians"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Give way to pedestrians"
        },
        {
            "id": 271,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "You can refrain from taking the drug or alcohol test:",
            "answers": [
                "In emergency cases",
                "If you are under 21",
                "No, you cannot in any case it may be"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No, you cannot in any case it may be"
        },
        {
            "id": 272,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When driving in the fog, you should turn on the:",
            "answers": [
                "High beam",
                "Hazard lights, and/or low beam",
                "Hazard lights, and/or high beam"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Hazard lights, and/or low beam"
        },
        {
            "id": 273,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When overtaking on a multiple  lane highway:",
            "answers": [
                "No need to give a signal",
                "Keep your eyes on the parallel lane",
                "Make sure there is enough gap in the lane you want to move to"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Make sure there is enough gap in the lane you want to move to"
        },
        {
            "id": 274,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you are taking a curve:",
            "answers": [
                "Maintain the speed of your veihcle",
                "Increase the speed of your vehicle",
                "Decrease the speed of your vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Decrease the speed of your vehicle"
        },
        {
            "id": 275,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the traffic lights are not working:",
            "answers": [
                "Act as if you are at an intersection without traffic lights",
                "Give the right of way to the driver on the left",
                "Stop and wait until the police gets to the intersection"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Act as if you are at an intersection without traffic lights"
        },
        {
            "id": 276,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When a truck is trying to overtake your vehicle:",
            "answers": [
                "Maintain or decrease your speed",
                "Change lanes",
                "Increase your speed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Maintain or decrease your speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 277,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "if you are moving behind a motorcycle, you should:",
            "answers": [
                "Allow the motorcycle to use half the lane",
                "Overtake the motorbike on the same lane",
                "Allow the motorbike to use the entire width of the lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Allow the motorbike to use the entire width of the lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 278,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If two drivers are approaching an intersection from opposite directions",
            "answers": [
                "The driver coming from the right should give the right of way to the other driver",
                "The driver coming from the left should give the right of way to the other driver",
                "Each will go on his way without giving priority to the other"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver coming from the left should give the right of way to the other driver"
        },
        {
            "id": 279,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Before overtaking, entering a curve, or being overtaken, you should",
            "answers": [
                "Reduce your speed, give a signal as you take the other lane",
                "Slow down, give enough signal to other road users, and check the mirrors and the blind spots",
                "Reduce your speed, give a signal to other drivers, and check the mirrors"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slow down, give enough signal to other road users, and check the mirrors and the blind spots"
        },
        {
            "id": 280,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When overtaking, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Disaccommodate drivers traveling on his right",
                "Use the right side of the road",
                "Use the left side of the road"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Use the left side of the road"
        },
        {
            "id": 281,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When a vehicle is turning and a pedestrian is crossing the street, and there is no traffic light, who has the right of way?",
            "answers": [
                "Whomever goes faster and reachs first",
                "The vehicle",
                "The pedestrian"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The pedestrian"
        },
        {
            "id": 282,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "Ice forms quickly on roads that:",
            "answers": [
                "Are plane",
                "Have an uneven surface, with lots of bends",
                "Are shaded"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Are shaded"
        },
        {
            "id": 283,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Travel in other than the designated direction",
                "Stay awake and in control of their vehicles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Travel in other than the designated direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 284,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Travel on the right side of the road",
                "Wash their vehicles on the higway"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Wash their vehicles on the higway"
        },
        {
            "id": 285,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Travel in the designated direction",
                "Make a U turn on the high way",
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Make a U turn on the high way"
        },
        {
            "id": 286,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Common logic dictates that you should not:",
            "answers": [
                "Go beyond the upper speed limit of 80 km/hour",
                "Go beyond the indicated speed limit",
                "Go faster than what is appropriate to the road you are traveling on"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Go faster than what is appropriate to the road you are traveling on"
        },
        {
            "id": 287,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "You can exit the road to overtake another vehicle",
            "answers": [
                "If the vehicle in front is turning left",
                "If the road or pedestrian lane can accomomdate you vehicle",
                "No, you cannot in any case it may be"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "No, you cannot in any case it may be"
        },
        {
            "id": 288,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "You can carry on on a yellow light if you are:",
            "answers": [
                "Behind a vehicle that has the right of way (ambulance, civil defence, firetruck)",
                "Turning right",
                "Already in the intersection"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Already in the intersection"
        },
        {
            "id": 289,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Travel on the right side of the road",
                "Check there is no danger before overtaking",
                "Repair vehicles on the freeway, except in extreme situations"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Repair vehicles on the freeway, except in extreme situations"
        },
        {
            "id": 290,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The driver should keep to the extreme right:",
            "answers": [
                "When the driver is traveling below traffic speed",
                "When the driver wants to overtake another vehicle",
                "When the driver has enough visibility ahead"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "When the driver is traveling below traffic speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 291,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers who have had their drivers license for more than three years, should not drive under the influence of alcohol where the level of alcohol in their blood exceeds:",
            "answers": [
                "0.5 grams/liter",
                "0.3 grams/liter",
                "0.4 grams/liter"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "0.5 grams/liter"
        },
        {
            "id": 292,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In the first three years of having a drivers license, the level of alcohol in the blood should not exceed:",
            "answers": [
                "0.5 grams/liter",
                "0 grams/liter",
                "0.3 grams/liter"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "0 grams/liter"
        },
        {
            "id": 293,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is strictly prohibited for drivers to:",
            "answers": [
                "Use any communication devices",
                "Use one hand to drive and the other to answer the phone",
                "Use both hands to drive, and answer the call using bluetooth technology"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Use any communication devices"
        },
        {
            "id": 294,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Where there is no speed limit signs, the upper speed limit on the freeway is:",
            "answers": [
                "100 km/hour",
                "120 km/hour",
                "80 km/hour"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "100 km/hour"
        },
        {
            "id": 295,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Where there is no speed limit signs, the upper speed limit outside populated areas is:",
            "answers": [
                "50 km/hour",
                "60 km/hour",
                "70 km/hour"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "70 km/hour"
        },
        {
            "id": 296,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Where there is no speed limit signs, the upper speed limit inside populated areas is:",
            "answers": [
                "40 km/hour",
                "50 km/hour",
                "60 km/hour"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "50 km/hour"
        },
        {
            "id": 297,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "You can reverse on the freeway if the exist is near, provided you do not go faster than:",
            "answers": [
                "10 meters",
                "20 meters",
                "You cannot reverse at all"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You cannot reverse at all"
        },
        {
            "id": 298,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "On a normal road, you place the warning triangle in front or behind the vehicle, depending on the direction of traffic, at the following distance from the vehicle:",
            "answers": [
                "20 meters",
                "30 meters",
                "40 meters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "30 meters"
        },
        {
            "id": 299,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "On the freeway, you place the warning triangle in front or behind the vehicle, depending on the direction of traffic, at the following distance from the vehicle:",
            "answers": [
                "70 meters",
                "50 meters",
                "60 meters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "50 meters"
        },
        {
            "id": 300,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Pedestrians should use pavements and pedestrians crossings and paths when they are at a distance of:",
            "answers": [
                "170 meters",
                "150 meters",
                "130 meters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "150 meters"
        },
        {
            "id": 301,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the driver causes an accident, and even if damages are material damages only:",
            "answers": [
                "The driver has the right to flee the scene and avoid responsibility",
                "The driver should carry on driving",
                "The driver should stop and take care of the victim"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver should stop and take care of the victim"
        },
        {
            "id": 302,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the brake lights are down:",
            "answers": [
                "All of the above",
                "The car may be impounded",
                "This is a Class 2 violation"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "All of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 303,
            "category": "Law",
            "question": "The shelf life of tyres does not exceed:",
            "answers": [
                "6 years from manufacturing date or 1.6 mm thread thickness, whichever comes first",
                "4 years from manufacturing date or 1.6 mm thread thickness, whichever comes first",
                "5 years from manufacturing date or 1.6 mm thread thickness, whichever comes last"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "6 years from manufacturing date or 1.6 mm thread thickness, whichever comes first"
        },
        {
            "id": 304,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the traffic light is green, but traffic is congested, road users should:",
            "answers": [
                "Move slowly so as not to obstruct traffic",
                "Cross the green light quickly",
                "Refrain from crossing the green light if it would obstruct traffic"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Refrain from crossing the green light if it would obstruct traffic"
        },
        {
            "id": 305,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A power of attorney to sell a vehicle is valid for not more than:",
            "answers": [
                "Two months",
                "Three months",
                "One month"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Two months"
        },
        {
            "id": 306,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "A broken line on the road means:",
            "answers": [
                "You cannot cross the line",
                "You can cross the line",
                "You can travel on the line"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "You can cross the line"
        },
        {
            "id": 307,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Vehicles of all types cannot be fitted in the front with lights other than:",
            "answers": [
                "Blue or yellow",
                "White or blue",
                "White or yellow"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "White or yellow"
        },
        {
            "id": 308,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the road is divided into two lanes with a yellow line, the driver should, in normal traffic situation:",
            "answers": [
                "Use the middle lane",
                "Use the left lane",
                "Use the right lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Use the right lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 309,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "If the lane is marked with a solid yellow line and a broken yellow line:",
            "answers": [
                "The driver can change lane if the solid line is to the right, and cannot change lane if the broken line is to the right",
                "The driver cannot change lane if the solid or borken line is to the right",
                "The driver can change lane if the broken line is to the right, and cannot change lane if the solid line is to the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver can change lane if the broken line is to the right, and cannot change lane if the solid line is to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 310,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "The driver should give the right of way to:",
            "answers": [
                "Pedestrians",
                "Vehicles",
                "Trucks"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Pedestrians"
        },
        {
            "id": 311,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In steep descents, the right of way goes to:",
            "answers": [
                "vehicles moving downwards",
                "Vehicles moving upwards",
                "It depends on the road itself"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Vehicles moving upwards"
        },
        {
            "id": 312,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Inside cities, you should always keep a safe distance of:",
            "answers": [
                "1 second",
                "2 meters",
                "2 seconds"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "2 seconds"
        },
        {
            "id": 313,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In entering a roundabout, the right of way is for:",
            "answers": [
                "The vehicle on the left",
                "The vehicle on the right",
                "The vehicle that is already in the roundabout"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The vehicle that is already in the roundabout"
        },
        {
            "id": 314,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Overtaking is not allowed in:",
            "answers": [
                "Mutliple lane tunnels",
                "Double lane tunnels",
                "Single lane tunnels"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Single lane tunnels"
        },
        {
            "id": 315,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In case of road works, the driver should:",
            "answers": [
                "Turn on his vehicle lights",
                "Drive fast",
                "Reduce speed"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Reduce speed"
        },
        {
            "id": 316,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Children below the age of five should be seated:",
            "answers": [
                "In their parents laps",
                "In the back seats",
                "In child seats"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In child seats"
        },
        {
            "id": 317,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When vehicles are still approaching an intersection, the right of way is always for the driver coming from:",
            "answers": [
                "Inside the intersection",
                "The left",
                "The right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The right"
        },
        {
            "id": 318,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When overtaking a motorbike, the driver should keep a side distance of no less than:",
            "answers": [
                "75 CM",
                "65 CM",
                "70 CM"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "75 CM"
        },
        {
            "id": 319,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When overtaking another vehicle, the driver should keep a side distance of no less than:",
            "answers": [
                "50 CM",
                "45 CM",
                "60 CM"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "50 CM"
        },
        {
            "id": 320,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are prohibited to obstruct traffic by:",
            "answers": [
                "Stopping slowly",
                "Travelling below the lower speed limit",
                "Stopping suddenly without a valid reason to do so"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Stopping suddenly without a valid reason to do so"
        },
        {
            "id": 321,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you meet head on with another vehicle on a two way road, who should reverse?",
            "answers": [
                "A group of vehicles for a single vehicle",
                "A single vehicle for a group of vehicles",
                "Heavy vehicles for a single vehicle"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "A single vehicle for a group of vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 322,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Who has the right of way on a three forked road?",
            "answers": [
                "The driver who proceeds cautiously",
                "The driver on the right side",
                "The driver who is on the straight lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver who is on the straight lane"
        },
        {
            "id": 323,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When you see on the freeway a sign that indicates that there is a road diversion or that the lane you are on will lead you to another direction, all drivers wishing to exist the lane should:",
            "answers": [
                "Swerve very quickly to the lane that will take them to the desired direction to avoid obstructing traffic",
                "Swerve immediately left or right to the lane that will take them to the desired direction to avoid obstructing traffic",
                "Swerve gradually left or right to the lane that will take them to the desired direction"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Swerve gradually left or right to the lane that will take them to the desired direction"
        },
        {
            "id": 324,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Seat belts should be fastened by passengers sitting:",
            "answers": [
                "In the front and back seats when on the highway, in all types of vehicles",
                "In the front seats, in all types of vehicles",
                "In the front and back seats, in all types of vehicles"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "In the front and back seats when on the highway, in all types of vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 325,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the traffic policeman lifts his hand vertically, it means:",
            "answers": [
                "You have to slow down",
                "Traffic ahead has come to a halt",
                "\"Careful and stop\" to all road users"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "\"Careful and stop\" to all road users"
        },
        {
            "id": 326,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the traffic policemans both hands are stretched horizontally, it means:",
            "answers": [
                "\"Stop\"    for all road users coming from directions that cross with the strecthed hands directions",
                "\"Slow down\"    for all road users coming from directions that cross with the strecthed hands directions",
                "\"Make Way\"    for all road users coming from directions that cross with the strecthed hands directions"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "\"Stop\"    for all road users coming from directions that cross with the strecthed hands directions"
        },
        {
            "id": 327,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Every vehicle should be fitted with",
            "answers": [
                "Two registration plates with the vehicle number, at the front and back sides of the vehicles",
                "A registration plate at the back side of the vehicle",
                "Two registration plates with the vehicle number, at front or back side of the"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Two registration plates with the vehicle number, at the front and back sides of the vehicles"
        },
        {
            "id": 328,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Up until the age of 50, the driver should renew his driving license, every",
            "answers": [
                "20 years",
                "5 years",
                "10 years"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "10 years"
        },
        {
            "id": 329,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Warning sounds can be used only:",
            "answers": [
                "To alert other drivers that they should move quickly",
                "To escape heavy traffic",
                "To alarm other road users so as to avoid accidents"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "To alarm other road users so as to avoid accidents"
        },
        {
            "id": 330,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "In case there is no sign that indicates which side of the vehicle should be used to step out of the vehicle",
            "answers": [
                "The passenger should step out from the side that is easier for his movement and that he deems appropriate",
                "The passenger should step in and out of the vehicle from the door that is on the same side of traffic",
                "The passenger should step in and out of the vehicle from the door that is on the other side of traffic"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The passenger should step in and out of the vehicle from the door that is on the other side of traffic"
        },
        {
            "id": 331,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the driver waives his hand up and down, it means:",
            "answers": [
                "Car brekadown",
                "Direction to the left",
                "Slow down and stop"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Slow down and stop"
        },
        {
            "id": 332,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the driver streches his hand horizontally, it means the driver is:",
            "answers": [
                "Reversing",
                "Turning left",
                "Slowing down"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Turning left"
        },
        {
            "id": 333,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the driver streches his hand vertically, it means:",
            "answers": [
                "Stop",
                "Direction to the left",
                "Direction to the right"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Direction to the right"
        },
        {
            "id": 334,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Vehicles turning right can cross a red light provided:",
            "answers": [
                "They stop at the traffic light, make sure they can cross without putting pedestrians and vehicles at risk",
                "They do it quickly",
                "Vehicles turning right cannot cross a red light"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "They stop at the traffic light, make sure they can cross without putting pedestrians and vehicles at risk"
        },
        {
            "id": 335,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "When the road is marked with solid lines:",
            "answers": [
                "The driver cannot change lanes",
                "The driver can change lanes, but has to do it quickly",
                "The driver can change lanes, provided he makes sure there is enough gap in the other lane"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "The driver cannot change lanes"
        },
        {
            "id": 336,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Children under cannot sit in the front seat:",
            "answers": [
                "10 years",
                "12 years",
                "8 years"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "10 years"
        },
        {
            "id": 337,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "It is strictly prohibited to throw stuff from the vehicle as this would:",
            "answers": [
                "Cause road markings to fade away",
                "Cause accidents, and clog water drainage system",
                "Obstruct policemen"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Cause accidents, and clog water drainage system"
        },
        {
            "id": 338,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "What is the difference between yellow lines and white lines when they are in the middle of the road?",
            "answers": [
                "Yellow lines are used on road sides only, whereas white lines are used to mark vehicle lanes",
                "Yellow lines are used for one way roads whereas white lines are used for two way streets",
                "White lines demarcate lanes that go in the same direction, yellow lines are demarcate lanes that go in opposite directions"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "White lines demarcate lanes that go in the same direction, yellow lines are demarcate lanes that go in opposite directions"
        },
        {
            "id": 339,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers cannot stop and park within a distance of from the top edge of ascent, curb, intersection, roundabout, and traffic light",
            "answers": [
                "50 meters",
                "30 meters",
                "25 meters"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "25 meters"
        },
        {
            "id": 340,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Transport expired bottles or cans o alcohol",
                "Transport in their vehicles bottles or cans of alcohol that have the manufacturer seal",
                "Transport in their vehicles unsealed bottles or cans of alcohol"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Transport in their vehicles unsealed bottles or cans of alcohol"
        },
        {
            "id": 341,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers should stop and park:",
            "answers": [
                "On white pedestrian crossing stripes",
                "After white pedestrian crossing stripes",
                "Before white pedestrian crossing stripes"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Before white pedestrian crossing stripes"
        },
        {
            "id": 342,
            "category": "Safety",
            "question": "Drivers are strictly prohibited to:",
            "answers": [
                "Travel on white lines",
                "Cross white broken lines",
                "Travel between white lines"
            ],
            "correctAnswer": "Travel on white lines"
        }
    ]
}